<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <string name = "app_name">Digitizer</string>
    <string name = "subtitle_prefix">em; lc:</string>

    <string name = "strategy">Building a strategy</string>
    <string name = "usp">Unique Benefits (USP)</string>
    <string name = "my_believe">The \ "I believe \" of my business</string>
    <string name = "kpi">Improvement with Goals</string>
    <string name = "google_business">Google Business Page</string>
    <string name = "posts">Posts (on social media and blog)</string>
    <string name = "content_marketing">content marketing</string>
    <string name = "website">Build a site</string>
    <string name = "sem">Post SEM</string>
    <string name = "ads">Posting in Media (Advertisements)</string>
    <string name = "mail">Email Marketing</string>
    <string name = "app">Using a smartphone</string>

    <string-array name="topics_id">
        <item>strategy</item>
        <item>usp</item>
        <item>my_believe</item>
        <item>kpi</item>
        <item>google_business</item>
        <item>posts</item>
        <item>content_marketing</item>
        <item>ads</item>
        <item>website</item>
        <item>sem</item>
        <item>mail</item>
        <item>app</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name = "strategy_subtitle">
                    In this unit we will build the strategy for promoting the business, by three main steps:

1. Goals - What do you want to achieve through your digital presence? (E.g., increase sales or brand recognition)

2. Mission Statement - What values ​​are important to the business? (E.g. Fair Trade or Environmental Protection)

3. Unique Business Advantages (USP - Unique selling proposition) - What makes the business unique compared to its competitors? (E.g. customer service, fixed price, or quality).
\ n
   </string>
    <string name = "usp_subtitle">
                    To help my clients understand why they should reach me, I need to understand the exact service I offer. When the customer buys, he goes through a process: "Seeing, thinking, doing, feeling" (See, Think, Do, Care). We must understand this process in order to connect with the customer.
\ n
     Think about the last product you bought online, then go back to the "see, think, do, feel" frame. Consider the following:
\ n
1. What prompted you to get interested in the product? (See)
\ n
2. How did you do your research? (Think)
\ n
3. What eventually made you press the buy button? (Do)
\ n
4. Have you left a review or posted a picture of the product online? (Feel).

   </string>
    <string name = "my_believe_subtitle">
           Creating a believing self of the business is an important step before jumping into the water and starting advertising. When a customer searches for a product, it checks to see if the product meets its need, in the best way, and connects to it.
\ n
            When we want to create a digital presence for the business, we must first of all explain in a sentence - who we are and why we bring the product that is right for the customer. Once we know how to set this up for ourselves, we can use it in our advertising and representation on the network, enabling the customer to connect with the business.
   </string>
    <string name = "kpi_subtitle">
                    Developing key performance indicators (or KPIs) is a necessary tool for understanding whether my business is progressing and meeting my goals.
\ n
This is a quantitative metric that allows me to focus on the most important criteria for achieving business goals.
\ n
How do you do that?
            \ n
            KPIs should be specific, measurable, achievable, relevant and limited in time. This is called the SMART framework.
   </string>
    <string name = "website_subtitle">
            The goal of the search engine is to find for the user exactly what they are looking for on the web. But how does it work?
            \n\n
The engines search for as much information as possible about the sites:
            \n\n
- How popular the sites are
            \n\n
- What other people or sites say about them
            \n\n
- Examine words that appear on the webpages or keywords found in the page code to better understand the topic.
            \n\n
- Geographic location of the user
\n\n
            Find the metrics that will help people find the business website the easiest.
   </string>
    <string name = "app_subtitle">
                    Did you know that the first call on a mobile phone was made in 1973? Just 11 years later, in 1984, the first commercial mobile phone market came out. It was a Motorola device that sold for a staggering 2,500 pounds! Since then, the field of mobile phones has evolved significantly. The devices were reduced and more and more features were added. Today they are an essential part of our daily lives. Mobile phones have long been not just phones, but multifunctional multimedia devices. They can be used to browse the Internet, read emails, take photos, navigate with GPS, post social media content and much more. The mobile devices have changed so much in recent decades that there is no way to know what the future holds. Mobile use is still expanding. A little less than a quarter of the world’s population will already be using smartphones this year. By 2018, more than a third of the world\'s population will use smartphones. That\'s more than two billion and a half people!
\n\n
Mobile devices and tablets are so useful and convenient that it\'s not surprising that we use them more and more. This year, UK adults will spend an average of two hours and 26 minutes a day on mobile. That is, for the first time we have come to the point that we use these devices more than desktops and laptops. Today, mobile users are even sitting watching TV with a smartphone in hand, and are more active than ever on social media. What is the business significance of all this data? Marketers need to get to where customers are, and currently customers are on mobile phones.
\n\n
Mobile devices and tablets are so useful and convenient that it\'s not surprising that we use them more and more. We have come to the point that we use these devices more than desktops and laptops.
\n\n
what is the meaning?
Marketers need to get to where customers are, and currently customers are on mobile phones.

How do you do that?
            \ n
Responsive site - optimized.
            \ n
- Operation link
            \ n
- Direct phone call
            \ n
- Apps
\ n
   </string>
    <string name = "sem_subtitle">
                    These are messages that appear at the top of the page and are displayed by using certain keywords.
Payment is just about every click, and not just the show.

When using search engine marketing, people who click on your ad are most likely to be interested in what you have to offer because they have told you that is what they are looking for. I mean, that\'s what they said to the search engine when they searched for "Tel Aviv wedding photographer", saw the ad and clicked on it. Unlike traditional marketing methods, search engine marketing targets people who are looking for products or services.

The text ads that appear on search engine results pages. Each time someone searches, advertisers compete for the chance to show ads. This happens within milliseconds, and the searcher does not see the details, but only the winners: the ads that appear on the page.

How do the search engines decide who will win? The main factors are:
1. The quote.
2. The quality.

The bid is the maximum amount that an advertiser is willing to pay for a click on their ad. If someone clicks on the ad, the advertiser is charged or sometimes less than the bid amount. So if an advertiser bids for $ 2 per keyword, that\'s the maximum they\'ll pay for a single click.
\ n
Bids are important, but quality is just as important. Not always the highest bidder will win the auction. The search engines reward ads and keywords that are very relevant to the search term. In fact, relevant ads may "win" higher positions on the search results page, even with lower bids. In some cases, even if the bid is very high, the search engine will not show the ad if it is irrelevant.
        \ n
   </string>
    <string name = "ads_subtitle">
                    Display advertising can be likened to a digital version of a billboard, print ad, or TV commercial. Businesses pay the owners of "space" for ad serving in the hope that their ads will show to the right people, and those people will become customers.
\ n
There are many methods to execute these transactions. You can make a deal directly with a site owner, or use networks that "link" between businesses and different sites that have space to display ads for sale. You can decide to show ads on specific web pages or to specific people, or even both.
\ n
   </string>
    <string name = "google_business_subtitle">
                    Google Business, is a fundamental and significant milestone in creating digital presence. When you search for your business name on Google, the business page will appear immediately and provide important details - such as location, opening hours, products and even prices. It is an initial and meaningful way of advertising - simple and free.
   </string>
    <string name = "content_marketing_subtitle">
                    There are loads of businesses on the internet, so it is very important to stand out. Content-based marketing is a great way to attract the attention of the audience. In this lesson, we will see why content-based marketing is important and how it can be used to engage with the audience. In addition, we’ll show you best practices to help you create content-based marketing campaigns.
\ n
Content-based marketing creates and shares online content, such as videos, blogs, and social networking posts. Its goal is to generate interest in the company\'s products or services by attracting the audience\'s attention.
\ n
Today people can choose when to interact with the brand (engagement), and content-based marketing allows businesses to connect with audiences in a way that has never been possible before.
\ n
You can post interesting content about dogs on your blog site, and promote it on the company\'s social media platforms so that more people read the content.
The more you know about the audience and understand their interests and needs, the easier it will be to arouse interest on a personal level.
\ n
How to do it?
            \ n
1. Answer the questions of the audience
            \ n
2. Provide something valuable
            \ n
3. Engage the audience for more content
\ n
Avoid business language and stencil responses, preferring natural formulations to stimulate audience interest. Create unique, interesting and exciting content. Use interesting headlines, attractive pictures and informative content to get the audience\'s attention.
\ n
   </string>
    <string name = "posts_subtitle">
        You can publish all kinds of content online:
            \ n
- success stories
\ n
            - eBooks
\ n
            - infographic
\ n
            - Pictures and clips
\ n
            - more and more
\ n
\ n
            No matter what content format you choose, the goal is always the same: to communicate with an audience. The audience in turn will engage, share, learn, and some users may even convert.
\ n
            - In many cases, blogging is started as a separate section of an existing site. Blogs may include original content or guest author content.
\ n
            - Infographic is a great and informative method for visually displaying information. Infographic is very suitable for the Internet because it is a format that attracts attention and can be used to present complex or specialized content creatively.
\ n
            - eBooks can serve as informational guides that are easy to read and focus on a specific topic. This format provides readers with useful content and can help you stand out as an expert in your field.
\ n
            - Videos can include any type of content, from product demos to tutorials and customer stories. They allow brand advertisers to create interesting, entertaining and useful content that can be viewed anywhere.
\ n
            The next step is to think about what the main goal you want to achieve with the content. Generally, when engaging in content-based marketing, content creates four main goals that are:
\ n
            - to entertain
\ n
            - To inspire
\ n
            - Teach
\ n
            - Convince
\n\n

Let\'s use the example to explain how different content formats fit the goals you want to achieve with them:
            \ n
            Amber runs a hairdresser for dogs and wants to develop a content strategy that will help her highlight the presence of business on the Internet. To entertain the audience, she decides to post on social media funny clips of dogs doing stunts. To inspire, she plans to open a forum on the site, where people can post questions and get insights from her and other pet-raising people. To teach the audience, she shares blog posts. The posts include important dog care tips and dog nutrition tips. To convince people to use her services, she will share satisfied customer stories and ebooks that will showcase her knowledge and expertise in grooming. In a scenario that is relevant to your business, try to think which formats are best for achieving the specific goals you set for publishing content.

        \ n
   </string>
    <string name = "mail_subtitle">
                    We are all flooded with a wide variety of products today. If you want your product to occupy an important place in customer awareness, you should use email marketing. Email marketing is a great addition to the other digital marketing activities. Why? Because it fosters customer loyalty and engagement without the need for high financial investment and works well on mobile.
\ n
            The best way to start is to make a list of people who have expressed an interest in your business.
            \ n
How to do it?
            \ n
- Offer them information on discounts and promotions if they provide an email address.
            \ n
- If you have a website, you can include a form and encourage visitors to subscribe to the site. (It\'s important to remember that users should give you permission to send them commercial emails, and in many countries there are laws that require this consent.)
\n\n
More tips:
            \ n
- It shouldn\'t overwhelm users - otherwise they treat it as spam. You should start with a friendly "Hello" message in which you introduce yourself. Then, you can submit information about the store and the products you sell.
\ n
- When you have information about your customers, you can send them specific offers or content that may interest them.
\ n
- As you tell customers about your business, you can use marketing emails to get to know them better, too. You can ask your subscribers if they would like updates on other products or services. Then you can find out how they prefer to hear from you. For example, do they prefer to receive emails once a week or once a month? You can save this information in your mailing contacts database for future email marketing campaigns.
\ n
- Old-time customers will be happy to be notified of things that interest them - and most importantly, if you can expect what they want in advance.
\ n
- You can use email to solicit feedback from your contacts about your shopping or customer service experience and respond directly to them. If you know what worked well and what failed, you can offer solutions to their problems, or simply thank them for choosing to buy from you.
\ n
   </string>

    <string-array name = "topic_strategy_task">
        <item>
            Write at least three goals that I want to achieve with the digital presence (fishing - more calls, sales, ordering, etc.):
       </item>
        <item>Write - What ingredients do I already have? How are customers coming to me right now?</item>
        <item>What are the ways I attract customers today? How do I want to do this in the future?</item>
        <item>Choose the places you want to develop a digital presence</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_strategy_text">
        <item>Formulating a program is the most difficult and challenging phase - after which it runs.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            There are endless options, so you need to set some goals. With their help, we will know what are the best ways to get there.
       </item>
        <item>

           </item>
        <item>

       </item>
        <item>
            Ways to find you online:

1. Search Engines:
          <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- "Search Engine Optimization":
            SEO (Search Engine Optimization)
It helps to promote the site freely.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
The best way to do this - understanding what the best keywords are - are used by people.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Sponsored Marketing - SEM. This way, you buy advertising space on the search page.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. Sponsored advertising online. You can choose the type of sites and the type of advertisements.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
3. Membership networks - Connect with a lot of customers and build a digital presence page.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
4. Email Marketing. It\'s not about spam - but about people who say they want to get a marketing email - coupons, events, etc. can be posted
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
The more digital touch points you have - the more likely you are to reach more customers!
</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_strategy_extra">
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>aim_places</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_usp_task">
        <item>Who is my target audience?</item>
        <item>Who are my competitors?</item>
        <item>What are my target audience issues?</item>
        <item>How do I resolve these issues?</item>
        <item>Business Strengths:</item>
        <item>The points that require business improvement:</item>
        <item>Business Opportunities:</item>
        <item>What threatens my business?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_usp_text">
        <item>The key questions to ask when defining a unique advantage are:</item>
        <item>
            It\'s time to see what competitors are doing. Take this activity ten minutes from your agenda and search for the following "terms" in the search engine:
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
1. Business Name - Searching for a business name will let you know who is competing in terms of keywords and branding.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. Product or Service - Searching for a product or service will let you know who the competitors are when it comes to a product or service.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
3. Specify your location - The location will highlight competitors who are local to you and offer the same services.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
These "search terms" are used as "keywords" associated with a brand or product. People search for business or products on the web using these keywords, so it\'s important to know who else is showing up when customers use them.

       </item>
        <item>What\'s my customers need?</item>
        <item>What are my Unique Benefits (USP)?</item>
        <item>
            SWOT analysis will help you in wording, and will enable you to make more informed business decisions. The SWOT model addresses four factors: the strengths, weaknesses, opportunities and threats.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
You have to ask yourself:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            1. What are we good at?
       </item>
        <item>2. What does need improvement?</item>
        <item>3. What will lead to growth, change, and improvement?</item>
        <item>4. What factors, internal or external, existing or potential, could harm the business?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_usp_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_my_believe_task">
        <item>
            Add a business or brand description, such as "Local Pet Shop"
       </item>
        <item>Add a service like "Top quality dog ​​training equipment and accessories"</item>
        <item>Add what makes you special, like "high level of expertise"</item>
        <item>Add the desired result to your customers, such as "give new owners a sense of security"</item>
        <item>
            The "I believe" formulation of the business:
       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_my_believe_text">
        <item>

       </item>
        <item>

           </item>
        <item>

       </item>
        <item>

</item>
        <item>Formulation I believe in my business. It could be a sentence, or a paragraph.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            This answer should be in a language that is appropriate for the target audience of the business, it should be well worded and include the strengths and weaknesses of your business
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            At this point, the content mission statement is similar to the following statement: "As a local pet store, we want to provide expert content and quality dog ​​training equipment to enable you to become the best owner of your pet."
       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_my_believe_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>believe</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_kpi_task">
        <item>What exactly do I want to achieve? Measurable target. (Specific)</item>
        <item>How can the target achievement be measured practically? (Measurable)</item>
        <item>Is this a realistic goal? (Achievable)</item>
        <item>Is this relevant to my overall purpose? (Relevant)</item>
        <item>What is the target execution date? (Time-bound)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_kpi_text">
        <item>Example:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
So what does KPI look like in reality? Get to know Ryan. He owns a gym network called Fit Gym. He has to make sure he has enough customers to keep his business growing. To that end, Ryan wants at least 50 new members to join each of the chain\'s branches each month. That\'s his destination. To achieve that goal, Ryan needs to set KPI metrics that measure his team’s efforts to reach that goal. Ryan mapped out the actions the sales team can do to improve gym enrollment rates, and defined the following CPI metrics.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
The sales team should:
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Contact 20 prospects a day
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Respond to any referrals on social networks and email within 15 minutes of receiving them, during business hours
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Renew or upgrade 8 existing subscribers per month.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
By analyzing the results against the CPI metrics, Ryan will be able to know exactly which employees meet expectations and who needs additional sales guidance.
       </item>
        <item>ה</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_kpi_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_website_task">
        <item>What are the most targeted search words for you? This is part of Search Engine Optimization (SEO) - promoting the site on the web with its search content matching.</item>
        <item>Domain selection:</item>
        <item>What content will be on your site? Try to give a few headlines to the pages (for example: services, who we are, contact)</item>
        <item>Opening paragraph for pages, introduction, what it is etc:</item>
        <item>Page content. What will mainly be written content:</item>
        <item>Call-to-action / page actions / end / summary / links that you think are relevant to add:</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_website_text">
        <item>It is advisable that you tailor your site content to what people are actually looking for.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
You should include the terms people are looking for the most about your products. Just keep in mind that it may not be easy to differentiate your business with terms that are too popular in search.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
In addition, you should use detailed search words so that your business can be found specifically. And not just the field of business. For example - "plumbers - take care of your home every day!" Search engine optimization is called Long Tail.
       </item>
        <item>
            Domain is the name of the site displayed in English in the browser, for example: "google.com". The name should be related, short and catchy.
       </item>
        <item>
            When building a website, it is first necessary to decide which pages will be in it.
       </item>
        <item>Let\'s start filling the site with content. It is important that the content be even more important - relevant. When people search for things on the web, the search engine not only checks the keywords you have chosen, but also, and most importantly - the content of the site. Are the keywords in it? Are you dealing with topics relevant to your product? The more relevant the content on each page of the site is to you and what people are looking for - the more likely they are to find your site in search!</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_website_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>link</item>
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_app_task">
        <item>What do you mean by using the app?</item>
        <item>What pages will the app have?</item>
        <item>Calculate - What features are important to you in the app?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_app_text">
        <item>
            More and more businesses are also investing in app development to interact with customers everywhere.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
            Mobile-friendly sites include most of the features available on the main site, they are simply optimized for small screen play.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
            In contrast, smartphone apps are apps that can be downloaded and installed on mobile devices. Usually, apps provide a specific function that is not easy to run in a web browser.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
           </item>
        <item>
            Try to draw really, or imagine - if you are using the app that downloads, what do you expect to see there?
</item>
        <item>How is this helpful?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            - Push notifications by location / time / important events.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Accumulation of usage points
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Navigate to the scene
<![CDATA[<br>]]></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_app_extra">
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>pages</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_sem_task">
        <item>Look for ads of similar products. Which keywords did they choose? What did you write to find them?</item>
        <item>Think of keywords for your ads</item>
        <item>Try to formulate a single, relevant search ad that includes a call to action</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_sem_text">
        <item>
As with most auctions, bids are also bidding here and are affecting the results of the sale. But bidding isn\'t the only factor affecting the outcome. In this auction, the relevance of the ads is also a vital factor. That is, in order for an ad to be auctioned off, it has to make a good bid for it and it has to be very relevant to the search. Anyone who meets these two criteria can enjoy the benefits of search engine marketing.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
At least as important as the price is the relevance of the message. Maintaining relevance will help get the same results and even better ones - the most affordable.

       </item>
        <item>
To know if this is a good keyword, you need to check how many of these clicks are worth to your business. Checking the profits you make from ad clicks will help you understand which keywords are "good" for your business.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
- The relevance of the words you speak to you offers.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- A word that people will look for
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- On the one hand, the movement needs to be large, on the other hand enough unique words that you jump
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>

When creating a new search engine marketing campaign, it\'s important to understand what makes a keyword "successful". In this video, you\'ll learn what factors to consider when considering keyword bids, including:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- relevance
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- traffic
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Competition
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>

       </item>
        <item>
            So how do you create a special "catch your eye" ad?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Relevance - that\'s the name of the game. The most important. Try to formulate the title of your ad to be as similar as possible to the search term.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Score promotions
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
Call to Action (Buy / Order / Come). Research shows that people respond well when instructed on what to do. We recommend including the call-to-action on the second line of the ad so the searcher knows exactly what to do after clicking the ad. The wording guides the customers what to do when they visit the website and reinforces the relevance of the business to their needs.

       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_sem_extra">
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_ads_task">
        <item>What goals do you want to achieve with advertising?</item>
        <item>Think about ad headlines. What will make people who don\'t know you come in?</item>
        <item>Calculate what will make those who already know you want to learn more.</item>
        <item>Now these are people who are already interested in your product. Why is it worth them to reach you?</item>
        <item>What incentives can you offer customers to "convert" and buy from you?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_ads_text">
        <item>
First of all, you will probably use some platform for display advertising. This platform is a system that will allow you to advertise on different websites and help you create and run Display Network campaigns. On almost all platforms, you have the ability to decide where your ads will appear and who will see them.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
Finding the audience you want to target is an essential step, but you also need to create ads that will appear in a Display Network campaign.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
There is one important thing to remember: We recommend that you tailor the content to your targeted audience.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
Display advertising can be used to target very specific audiences, and even several audiences at once, depending on the message they want to convey. Making a decision about who you want to reach and what message you want to convey will help you both keep up with the campaigns and formulate the message, set the tone and shape the style of display advertising.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
           There are many advertising platforms, and you need to tailor them to your budget and needs. First, let\'s remember who our target audience is and where they are:
       </item>
        <item>

            If you set a few goals, one ad, or one campaign, you can\'t help them all. But there is no cause for concern. All you have to do is clearly define in advance what you want to achieve, and then you can create different ads that target different people for all the right reasons.

One of the simple ways to set the goals you want to achieve with Display Network advertising is to think about the different steps in converting the customer as a funnel.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
1. The biggest part of the funnel is ads - Display advertising will help you reach a wide audience.
It\'s time to think about how to draw attention. Remember, ads are shown to people who are not looking for you at that moment.
       </item>
        <item>
            2. Next in the funnel you need to help people formulate an opinion about you and make sure they remember you in the future. You can create a new display advertising campaign and deliver messages that highlight your competitive edge and highlight the benefits of each product or service you offer. At this point, you can narrow your audience down to include people who have already visited your site or people who are very interested in the products and services you offer.
</item>
        <item>
            3. The next step in the sales funnel is to focus on people who are already considering using your solution. At this point you can really distill your message and focus on features that make your product or service a great solution. These ads will be shown to people you know have shown interest in what you have to offer.
</item>
        <item>
            4. The last step in the sales funnel is the purchase. If your ultimate goal is to convince people to buy from you, you should focus on conversions. For example, you can create ads that offer special offers or incentives, and target them to people you know have shown interest but haven\'t bought yet.
       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_ads_extra">
        <item>ads_pages</item>
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_google_business_task">
        <item>Business name - what to look for to see it. Try to get the most accurate name, but also be unique and those who are looking for you - will find you:</item>
        <item>Phone / Phone Number</item>
        <item>address</item>
        <item>opening hours</item>
        <item>Business Description</item>
        <item>logo</item>
        <item>Photos of the business (not mandatory, but important!)</item>
        <item>Check when you opened the</item>page
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_google_business_text">
        <item>
            Creating a Google Business Page is an easy and straightforward process. Make sure you have the following:
       </item>
        <item>
            In addition, make sure you have the following:
</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>
            It\'s time to open your business page! When you do this, you will be sent a letter with a business page activation code (usually takes in the fortnightly area) - and you can then edit the rest of the business details.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        Remember! The more active the page is (posts can be shared - recommended on a weekly basis at least!), With more information - and you will respond to comments and messages sent to you - the more it will appear on the search page and get more views!
        <![CDATA[<br>]]><![CDATA[<br>]]>
        It\'s time to open the page:
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://www.google.com/business/">Opening Google Business Page!</a>]]>
       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_google_business_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_content_marketing_task">
        <item>Remember to set up your business</item>
        <item>Segment the audience into groups. What groups do you have? Try to be as accurate as possible.</item>
        <item>1. Their age:</item>
        <item>2. Their roles at work</item>
        <item>3. Their interests</item>
        <item>4. What’s important to them</item>
        <item>5. To what extent this topic is already familiar to them</item>
        <item>6. Where to find them? On what social networks?</item>
        <item>Got it!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_content_marketing_text">
        <item>
            To create high-quality content, you should define your metrics in terms of the content you create. Reminder for setting up your business:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
       </item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>
            When you go online to create content, you should think about who your audience is and what they want to know. Audience segmentation can help you do that.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
Segmentation means dividing your audience into groups of people by who they are and what they like. Instead of investing time and money in targeting a broad spectrum of people, segmentation helps identify the groups that are most interested in your product or service. The result is a more lucrative and compelling way to reach potential customers.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
When you understand the habits and preferences of a particular audience, the content can be targeted directly to that specific group of people.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
To know what people are looking for, try using free online tools like Answer The Public and keyword planner. You can use the features available on social media channel platforms, such as Facebook and Twitter, to get a quick look at demographics and audience behaviors. You may want to try some tools and compare the results to get a fuller picture of who your audience is and how they are performing online.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
Don\'t forget to talk to people. In the online world we live in, it\'s easy to forget, but talking to people face-to-face can provide you with unique insights into their identity and needs.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_content_marketing_extra">
        <item>believe</item>
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>population</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_posts_task">
        <item>Try to write a short opening</item>
        <item>Who is the target audience you are writing to now?</item>
        <item>Something that will generate interest in the post? (Main content)</item>
        <item>Formulate a call to action</item>
        <item>Choose one way to manage your blog publishing program. This can also be done manually - but make sure to schedule!</item>
        <item>As it is important to know what to do, it is important to know what not to do</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_posts_text">
        <item>
Reading habits on the Internet can be very different from reading habits on other channels. Style, length and structure are important considerations to consider when writing to different channels. For your readers to be interested in your content, we recommend that you tailor your writing to the Internet.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
We need to be quick and efficient: We are flooded with information. Our need to do several things at the same time and consume data from the Internet quickly and efficiently has made us spend less time on everything.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
How do you do that?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            We will try to go through the steps together.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            1. It is advisable to start with a short and attractive opening to explain to the reader what he can expect. It is important to draft an attractive opening paragraph or opening sentence to keep people reading. An example of an attractive opening could be a statistic.
       </item>
        <item>2. Don\'t forget who your target audience is</item>
        <item>3. Create interest</item>
        <item>4. Another important tip is to incorporate Call-To-Action content. Calls to action are short statements aimed at convincing a site visitor to perform a particular action, so it is worthwhile to put them in the most creative and compelling way. An example of a call to action can be \ "go ahead, work \" or \ "sign up today \".</item>
        <item>Serious investment in social media activity requires a lot of work, and anyone who doesn\'t have a clear plan can lose focus very quickly.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
It is not easy to keep up-to-date with the materials, answer and network with friends, or keep thinking of new, unique and interesting ideas for publications on several networks.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
You should create a cohesive plan - otherwise you will not meet your goals. It is difficult to build on "spontaneous" and high-quality content.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
So how to build a social media plan?
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
            How do you do this?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
Social media management tools such as Hootsuite, Buffer and Everypost can be used to pre-create sharing and advertising items.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            When using these tools, you have the ability to decide which network you want to share the items you created and collaborate with co-workers to help the success of social media advertising. In addition, you can use these tools to track people\'s reactions to your social media posts.

            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            Here are some options with free programs:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "http://everypost.me/">First Option: everypost</a>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://buffer.com/">Second option: buffer</a>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://hootsuite.com/">Third option: hootsuite</a>]]>

            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://www.wordstream.com/blog/ws/2018/01/17/best-free-social-media-management-tools">You can also find more tools here < / a>]]>

       </item>
        <item>
            And in conclusion:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            What not to do?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
1. People are not there for you. Brands whose content they provide are familiar, boring people and they stop referring to their publications fairly quickly. You need to focus on providing users with a good experience and not losing their attention. You need to tell followers what\'s new, what new merchandise is coming and how the business works. There is no need to make copies of your product pages and try to push them to people.

We recommend that you keep your hands on the web to know when people are responding to you, and allocate resources to respond to comments. You should always respond with understanding and consideration, but most importantly be consistent.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. Don\'t overuse social media. There are a lot of social media networks and there are almost endless options to talk to customers, but time should be spent on such things. If you are not careful, you will find yourself struggling to operate too many pages on social media sites. Focus on the most important networks and expand your activity only when expansion is required and you have the resources to do so.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
3. Do not get to the point that your page is not updated too long.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
4. A final recommendation, and very important, is to check what profit you are generating from social media activity.
       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_posts_extra">
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>radioContentMarketing</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "topic_mail_task">
        <item>The first step in email marketing is to set goals:</item>
        <item>Choose the best email marketing whistle for you</item>
        <item>Try to formulate a subject line for your marketing email</item>
        <item>Try wording your content to your marketing email</item>
        <item>These services can be performed using the software or website you use</item>
        <item>Got it!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_mail_text">
        <item>
            As with all things, in order for it to work, the most important thing is to build an orderly plan.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            The first step in email marketing is to set goals:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- display products?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Bring more customers?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Distributing promotions?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Get more sales?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
       </item>
        <item>
            There are many options to choose from, but most email marketing tools share some common features. The first is a contact database, which stores customer information. At the very least, the database should include an email address for each contact. Most programs allow you to include more information, such as name, mailing address, and other information.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
To start building your email marketing database, add the customer data you already have. Most services allow you to upload data from a spreadsheet, a useful feature if you have a lot of information to add.
Then you should offer people the option of subscribing (and unsubscribing) themselves. Most email services provide a digital form that can be added to the site by copying and pasting a short code snippet. Site visitors can submit this form to subscribe to your emails. This data is then automatically transferred to your contact database.
The digital sign-up form should be short and easy to fill.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
If you have customer information, you can use it to sort them into lists.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
After you build a database, let\'s think about the emails themselves. Email templates allow you to create a design that matches your brand.
Please note that the messages are optimized for mobile.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            Your email template can also include one or two fields for content specific to each group of specific pet owners. If you focus on each custom content group, you increase the chances that they will not only read the messages, but also click on the links to access your site.

            It\'s time to choose the service that\'s right for you! There are paid programs, and there are free ones, I will offer several options here. Think about it.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            Here are some options with free programs:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://www.sender.net/">First option: sender</a>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://mailchimp.com/">Second option: mailchimp</a>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://www.inwise.co.il/">Third option: inwise</a>]]>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://www.omnisend.com/">Fourth Option: omnisend</a>]]>

            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
            <![CDATA[<a href = "https://sproutsocial.com/insights/free-email-marketing-tools/">You can also find more tools here</a>]]>
</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
         1. How can you use so-called A / B testing to get more people to open your emails and click on links to your site?
what is it Anyway?
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
A / B tests are tests where you create two versions of an email to see which one performs better. You can use this method to try different approaches to email. You can send half of your customers version A of the subject line, and the other half of version B. Then you can check which version had a higher "opening rate".
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. A landing page is the first page a user sees when they arrive at your site. Thus, when someone clicks on a link from the email, they "land" on a relevant web page. Your email campaigns will be more successful if you direct visitors directly to the page they want to see so they can get product information and maybe buy it!
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
3. Keep in mind that people may read your messages on laptops, tablets, laptops, and desktops. This means that your message landing pages should work well on all these devices.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
4. It is important to use web data analytics to find out what users are doing on the site after clicking links from your messages.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
            The secret to success is to make a good first impression. Try to think about what customers see when they look in their inbox. Will your message make you want to open it? The two things they will see are:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
1. Your business name in the "From" field.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. The subject line of the message.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
It is important to make sure that the name and email address listed in the "From" field clearly identify your business.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
The message subject line can build or destroy the campaign:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- The subject line should be short and simple - preferably less than ten words. Try to encapsulate the most important and relevant information contained in the message.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Whenever possible, you may want to customize the subject line to the recipient personally or to their geographical area. For example: "Puppy, is your puppy the healthiest in London?"
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
Avoid words such as "free", "discount percentages", "reminder" and "promotions" as well as currency symbols (₪) and exclamation points. כל אלה ידועים כגורמים להפעלת מסנני דואר זבל.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
       </item>
        <item>
          Half way - content. Customers are busy and will only see the message in a snap:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- The content should be concise and go straight to the point. The paragraphs should be short - say one to three sentences - and focused on one idea.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- You can add links to longer articles and more information, which appear on your site.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Your writing should be as compelling and engaging as possible. The characterization of the language should suit your audience.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- The links in the email should include calls to action. For example, you can add a link like "Click here and save 25% off your next order of cat food, made from only natural ingredients." Or maybe "Click here for free shipping on orders over ₪ 50".
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- It is recommended to use bold text and prominent design to highlight important content and promotions.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>

       </item>
        <item>
            End of email:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
There is another component to include in your messages:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
- Links at the bottom of the email that allow recipients to unsubscribe from your messages, change their email preferences or update their contact information. Allowing you to easily unsubscribe from your newsletter is not only a good customer service, but also a legal requirement in many states.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
       </item>
        <item>
Analyzing the data from the email platform will provide you with information such as how many people clicked on an email link and moved to your site, or how many people performed actions that you included in calls to action, such as using a discount code to purchase on the site. Making informed decisions based on this kind of data can help you increase your conversion rate and improve future campaigns.
<![CDATA[<br>]]>
Main metrics:
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
1. Email Campaign "Start Rate" Index - The ratio of the number of people who opened the email to the total number of people who received it. From this figure you can understand how effective the subject line of the email is.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
2. CTR, also known as CTR - this metric gives you a general idea of ​​the success of a particular email campaign, and shows you the percentage of people who clicked links to your site from every email opened. The "CTR vs. Emails opened" metric refers to the total number of Clicks vs. actual opened emails.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
3. Conversion Rate - The conversion rate will show you how many people actually signed up for the event, out of all the people who received the email.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>
4. "Percent of emails that did not reach the recipient" - The percentage of emails that did not reach subscribers and were sent back. There are two types of repetition to distinguish: soft repetition: emails rejected because the inbox was full, or because of the size limit set on the audience email server. Hard repetition: Your emails are blocked or you are using an incorrect email address.
            <![CDATA[<br>]]>

       </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name = "topic_mail_extra">
        <item>pages</item>
        <item>radioMailMarketing</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>Enter here</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "market_palaces">
        <item>Google Business Page, and Social Networks</item>
        <item>posts (on social media and blog)</item>
        <item>Content-based marketing (social media, blogs and more)</item>
        <item>Media Advertising (Advertisements)</item>
        <item>site</item>
        <item>Search Engine Advertising (SEO)</item>
        <item>emails</item>
        <item>app</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "ContentMarketing">
        <item>Everypost</item>
        <item>Buffer</item>
        <item>Hootsuite‏</item>
        <item>Manually (prepare postage and content, and upload myself every time)</item>
        <item>something else</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "MailMarketing">
        <item>sender</item>
        <item>mailchimp</item>
        <item>inwise</item>
        <item>omnisend</item>
        <item>something else</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name = "market_formats">
        <item>social media posts</item>
        <item>Blog Postings</item>
        <item>Website Forum</item>
        <item>photos and clips</item>
        <item>ebooks</item>
        <item>infographic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name = "title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name = "prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name = "prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name = "action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name = "action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name = "welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name = "invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name = "invalid_password">Password must be>5 characters</string>
    <string name = "login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name = "title_activity_main_nav">mainNav</string>
    <string name = "navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name = "navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name = "nav_header_title">Digitizer</string>
    <string name = "nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name = "nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name = "action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name = "menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name = "menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name = "menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name = "menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name = "menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name = "menu_send">Send</string>

    <string name = "hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name = "open_page">
        Hi! Welcome to the Digitizer!
        \n\n
        Here we will help you promote the business with personal accompaniment, in the easiest and most important way - from time to time, maximum effect.
        \n\n
        In order to do this, you need to confirm the permissions to keep track of your progress, and create reminders in Google Calendar - so as not to forget your progress.
        \n\n
        Then you need to sign up, so you can save progress between devices.
        \n\n
        Thanks!
   </string>

    <string name="mail_choose_title">Email account selection</string>
    <string name="mail_choose_expl">
      Please select an email account so that we can keep the task alerts in the calendar.
\n\n
As you work on your business, we set tasks together. So that we can help you keep up with the events, we\'ll keep the events on Google\'s calendar. For this purpose, please select the account where we will store the events.
    </string>
    <string name="choose_mail">Select an email account</string>
    <string name="no_mail">No account selected</string>

    <string name="firebase_singIn">Sign in/Sign up</string>

    <string name = "app_package_name">com.icstudios.marketing assistant</string>

    <string name = "domain_check">You can check if the domain is available on this site. Enter the name and extension.</string>

    <string name = "remaind_to_goals">When choosing your digital presence, note that they match the goals you set. Reminder for your goals: </string>

    <string name = "last_assaingments">Please complete the previous tasks before performing this task!</string>

    <string name = "place_of_the_bussines">And, in light of where the business is already present: </string>

    <string name = "audience">Target audience: </string>

    <string name = "audience_exist">Where it is: </string>

    <string name = "my_belive_phrasing">
        As you formulate the "I believe" of the business, note that you are referring to the following:
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        Goals:
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
    </string>

        <string name = "where_to_publish">
        <![CDATA[<br>]]> <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        So where can I advertise? There are lots of options! Here are some significant examples:
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<a href = /"https://ads.google.com/"> Google Search Platform </a>:]]>
        One of the biggest advertising platforms is of course Google. Many sites and apps have Google advertising space. (In addition, the search is also valid for SEO ads on the Google search page and YouTube).
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<a href = /"https://www.facebook.com/business/ads"> Facebook Advertising Platform </a>:]]>
        Another great platform is Facebook. Here you can see the advertisements by user classification, ages, interests, etc.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<a href = /"https://business.instagram.com/advertising/"> Instagram Advertising Platform </a>:]]>
        Another significant social network is Instagram, which offers its own advertising channels.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<a href = /"https://www.waze.com/business/"> Wise Advertising Platform </a>:]]>
        Another creative way to advertise is Wiz Way, which offers local advertising services when the drivers are nearby.
    </string>

    <string name = "usp_string"> Your special benefits: </string>
        <string name = "audience_string"> Who is your target audience: </string>
        <string name = "how_are_you"> And of course who you are! Take a few minutes and put it well. Remember - this is what the customer will remember when he or she learns about you! </string>
        <string name = "summery_string">In summary, the "I believe" should look something like this: </string>
        <string name = "as">As</string>
        <string name = "provide"> We want to provide </string>
        <string name = "with"> combined with </string>
        <string name = "in_goal"> and purpose </string>
        <string name = "somtihng_else">something else</string>
        <string name = "exit">Exit</string>
        <string name = "exit_exp">Are you sure you want to leave? Don\'t forget, promoting your business requires no more than an hour a day!</string>
        <string name = "noti_title">Digitizer</string>
        <string name = "noti_head">Empty header</string>
        <string name = "noti_body1">Just a little more! You only left </string>
        <string name = "noti_body2"> tasks of </string>
        <string name = "noti_body3"> to finish this topic!</string>
        <string name = "hours">hours</string>
        <string name = "days">days</string>

    <string name = "enter_answer">Enter your answer here</string>
    <string name="add_button">Add box</string>
    <string name="remove_button">Remove box</string>


</resources>